{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Javascript is an _______ language?",
      "options": [
        "Object Oriented",
        "Object-Based",
        "Procedural",
        "None of the Above"
      ],
      "answer": "Object Oriented"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
      "options": ["Var", "Let", "Both A and B", "None of the Above"],
      "answer": "Both A and B"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
      "options": [
        "getElementById()",
        "getElementByClassName()",
        "Both A and B",
        "None of the Above"
      ],
      "answer": "Both A and B"
    },
    {
      "question": "Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
      "options": [
        "Throws an error",
        "Ignores the statements",
        "Give a warning",
        "None of the Above"
      ],
      "answer": "Ignores the statements"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
      "options": [
        "document.write()",
        "console.log()",
        "window.alert()",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
      "options": ["const", "var", "let", "constant"],
      "answer": "const"
    },
    {
      "question": "When the switch statement matches the expression with the given labels, how is the comparison done?",
      "options": [
        "Both the data type and and the result of the expression are compared",
        "Only the datatype of the exepression is compared",
        "Only the value of the expression is compared",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Both the data type and and the result of the expression are compared"
    },
    {
      "question": "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
      "options": ["in", "is in", "exists", "lies"],
      "answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the use of the '<'noscript'>' tag in Javascript?",
      "options": [
        "The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers",
        "clears all the cookies and cache",
        "Both A and B",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers"
    },
    {
      "question": "When an operator's value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
      "options": ["Boolean", "Undefined", "Object", "Integer"],
      "answer": "Object"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the Javascript “debugger” statement do?",
      "options": [
        "It will debug all the errors in the program at runtime",
        "It acts as a breakpoint in a program",
        "It will debug error in the current statement if any",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "It acts as a breakpoint in a program"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the 'toLocateString()' method do in JS?",
      "options": [
        "Returns a localised object representation",
        "Returns a parsed string",
        "Returns a localized string representation of an objcet",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Returns a localized string representation of an objcet"
    },
    {
      "question": "The process in which an object or data structure is translated into a format suitable for transferral over a network, or storage is called?",
      "options": [
        "Objcet Serialization",
        "Object Encapsulation",
        "Object Inheritance",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Objcet Serialization"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
      "options": ["Stringify()", "parse()", "convert()", "None of the above"],
      "answer": "Stringify()"
    },
    {
      "question": "The 3 basic object attributes in Javascript are:",
      "options": [
        "Class,prototype,objects's parameters",
        "Class,prototype,objects's extensible flag",
        "Class,parameters,objects's extensible flag",
        "Class,Native object, and Interfaces and extensible flag"
      ],
      "answer": "Class,prototype,objects's extensible flag"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
      "options": ["Variables", "Funactions", "Objects", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a Javascript framework?",
      "options": ["Node", "Vue", "React", "Cassandra"],
      "answer": "Cassandra"
    },
    {
      "question": "What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
      "options": ["async", "await", "setTimeout", "None of the above"],
      "answer": "async"
    },
    {
      "question": "How to stop an interval timer in Javascript?",
      "options": [
        "clearInterval",
        "clearTimer",
        "intervalOver",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "clearInterval"
    },
    {
      "question": "How are objects compared when they are checked with the strict equality operator?",
      "options": [
        "The contents of the objects are compared",
        "Their references are compared",
        "Both A and B",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Their references are compared"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does … operator do in JS?",
      "options": [
        "It is used to spread iterables to individual elements",
        "It is used to describe of undefined size",
        "No such operator exists",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "It is used to spread iterables to individual elements"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do we write a comment in javascript?",
      "options": ["/* */", "//", "#", "$$"],
      "answer": "//"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which object in Javascript doesn't have a prototype?",
      "options": [
        "Base Object",
        "All objects have a prototype",
        "None of the objects have a prototype",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Base Object"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following are not server-side Javascript objects?",
      "options": ["Date", "FileUpload", "Funstion", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet? print(NaN === NaN);",
      "options": ["true", "false", "Undefined", "Error"],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following are not server-side Javascript objects?",
      "options": ["Date", "FileUpload", "Function", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    }
  ]
}
